Guide to the Hannah Green Letters to Vincent McHugh, 1957-1959
Department of Special Collections
- Addendum
  - 1960, June (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - ALS, 2pp. (pencil) 6/10/60
    - ALS, 5pp. (pencil) 6/16/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 6/17/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 6/20/60
    - ALS, 4pp. (pencil) 6/22/60
    - ALS, 2pp. (pencil) 6/23/60
    - ALS, 2pp. (pencil) 6/27/60
  - 1960, July (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - ALS, 2pp. (pencil) 7/2/60
    - ALS, 2pp. (pencil) (Traverse City, MI) 7/6/60
  - 1960, August (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - ALS, 3pp. (Natick) 8/13/60
    - ALS, 5pp. (Boston) 8/18/60
    - ALS, 2pp. (pencil) 8/28/60
  - 1960, September (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - ALS, 3pp. (Boston) 9/5/60
    - ALS, 2pp. (Yonkers) 9/9/60
    - ALS, 5pp. 9/16/60
    - ALS, 6pp. (NYC) 9/23/60
    - ALS, 4pp. (Boston) 9/23/60
    - ALS, 3pp. (ink) (MacDowell Colony) Monday
    - ALS, 4pp. (NYC) Tues
  - 1960, October (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - ALS, 1p. (NYC) 10/8/60
    - ALS, 8pp. 10/11/60
    - ALS, 2pp. (MacDowell Colony) Tues
    - ALS, 5pp. 10/14/60
    - ALS, 1p. 10/23/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/30/60
    - ALS, 5pp. (pencil) 10/31/60
  - 1960, November (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - ALS, 1p. 11/2/60
    - ALS, 3pp. (MacDowell Colony) Thurs
    - ALS, 3pp. (pencil) (Peterborough) 11/7/60
    - ALS, 4pp. (pencil) (legal size) 11/12/60
    - ALS, 6pp. (pencil) 11/14/60
    - ALS, 4pp. (pencil) 11/14/60
    - ALS, 1p. (pencil) 11/30/60
  - 1961 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - ALS, 4pp. 8/16/61
    - ALS, 4pp. 8/25/61
    - ALS, 3pp. 9/15/61
    - ALS, 5pp. 10/10/61
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/13/61
    - ALS 4pp. (3pp. typed) 11/5/61
    - TLS, 2pp. (NYC) 11/10/61
  - Undated/Unclear Letters (Box 6, Folder 12)
    This folder contains seventeen letters which have unclear postmarks, thus cannot be filed with the other letters.
  - Vincent McHugh letters to Hannah Green (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - TLS, 7pp. 12/25/60
    - TLS, 3pp. 10/12/61
    - TLS, 2pp. 11/7/61